secret you're not telling me, you look different, right? Because they are different, right?
That's the joy of change, right? So the evening and the morning are two times in the day where
your the door opens up, you know, your brainwaves go from beta to alpha to theta to delta in the
evening. When you wake up in the morning, you know, you go from delta to theta to alpha to
beta. So there's two times where the door between the conscious mind and the subconscious
mind opens. And people, I mean, the people in my life that do this, they take their time before
they go to bed. They write things down that are important to them, things they want to change.
They don't want to watch TV or get on their device. They really want to invest in themselves, right?
And they're serious about it. And as a side effect, the opportunities, the coincidences,
the synchronicities, the serendipities somehow are coming to them. It's not like they're going